#### CONTACT



a.p.tkoy@gmail.com 630-363-0924

## DATA ANALYST AND SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

With a firm grasp of computer science fundamentals, I quickly adjust to new programming languages and problem solving challenges. I push my boundaries to achieve worthy goals, as evidenced in restarting my education to earn a second bachelor's degree in Statistics and Computer Science. Most of all, I love to collaborate because working with amazing people has been the highlight of all my prior career experiences.

#### **SKILLS**

- Programming in C, C++, Java, OCaml, Python, and R
- Analyzing data to produce summary findings and visualizations
- Took lead as front-end developer for project creating web app with React, Node.js and Javascript
- Completed additional coursework outside degree in SQL and Swift programming
- Version control with GitHub
- Video editing, motion graphics and graphic design

#### **EDUCATION**

## UNIVERSITY OF ILLINOIS URBANA CHAMPAIGN

Bachelor of Science Statistics and Computer Science 3.91 GPA

# DEPAUL UNIVERSITY

Bachelor of Science Marketing 3.94 GPA

## COLLEGE OF DUPAGE

Associate in Applied Science Film/Video Production 4.0 GPA

#### EXPERIENCE

#### GENIUS ADMIN, MAR 2022 - AUG 2023

Apple Store, Naperville, IL

- Resolved and escalated issues for in-store repairs
- Managed flow of repairs to and from offsite repair facility
- Maintained organization and inventory of repair room
- Collaborated across store teams to ensure excellent customer experiences

## APPLE CAREER EXPERIENCE, JAN 2023 - JUN 2023

Apple, Inc., Cupertino, CA

Supported the Manufacturing Quality Engineering, Color team for 5 months, full-time:

- Organized part samples for archive or recycling
- Operated special equipment to measure samples for color and texture
- Cleaned and manipulated data in Tableau to generate summary reports and visualizations
- Assisted in sample reviews with Industrial Design team

## PRODUCT SPECIALIST, NOV 2019 - MAR 2022

Apple Store, Naperville, IL

Efficiently created solutions for customers, including scheduling repair/support appointments, recommending purchases, and facilitating initial device set up

## PROGRAM SUPPORT SPECIALIST, DEC 2017 - NOV 2019

College of DuPage, Glen Ellyn, IL

- Analyzed student data to create or update statistical reports each semester
- Updated 3 internal data resource websites using HTML